咖啡
Coffee.
谢谢      卡布奇诺
Thank you.        Cappuccino.
摩妮卡的热苹果酒
And a nice hot cider for Monica.
谢谢
Aw, thank you.
瑞秋      嗯?
Rach?        Yeah?
我的肉桂棒怎么有橡皮擦?
Why does my cinnamon stick have an eraser?
哦!
Oh.
哦 难怪
That's why.
对不起
I'm sorry.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第01季 第15集
大麻客 The One With the Stoned Guy
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：悠悠慕雪
钱德?
Chandler?
泰德拉克小姐 你今天真漂亮
Miss Ted lock, you're looking lovely today.
我能说你这件衣服真好看么?
May I say that is a very flattering sleeve length on you?
是的
Yes.
卡斯力克先生要你在下班前去他办公室
Well, Mr. Costilick wants you to stop by his office at the end of the day.
如果是有关搞笑备忘录 我跟那一点关系也没有
Oh, listen, if this is about those prank memos, I had nothing to do with them.
真的 跟我无关 真的
Really, nothing at all. Really.
无关
Nothing.
各位! 嘿
Hey, you guys. You guys.
钱德要来了 他说他有个天大的消息
Chandler's coming, and he says he has, like, this incredible news.
所以等他到了 我们要假装 你们懂的
So when he gets here, let's all act like, you know
嗨      嗨
Hey.        Hey.
算了 但一定是好消息
Never mind. But it was gonna be really good.
到底怎么了?怎么了?
What's going on? What's is it?
今天和平时一样 我在输入数字时
So, it's a typical day at work. I'm inputting my numbers
艾尔叫我到他办公室
and Big Al calls me into his office,
告诉我他要给我升职 当电脑处理主管
and tells me he wants to make me processing supervisor.
太好了      恭喜!
That is great!        Congratulations.
所以我辞职了
So... I quit.
为什么?      为什么?
Why?        Why?
为什么?因为这只是个暂时的工作
Why? This was supposed to be a temp job.
钱德 你在那工作了5年了
Yeah, Chandler, you've been there for five years.
我知道 但如果我接受升职
I know. But if I took it this promotion,
那就表示我就是要干这个
it'd be like admitting that this is what I actually do.
那不是赚更多钱么
So was it a lot more money?
那不重要 我只是不想成为那种加班到半夜12点
It doesn't matter. I just don't want to be one of those guys that's in his office until 12:00 at night
担心"WENUS"的人
worrying about the WENUS.
"WENUS"是什么?
"The WENUS"?
周估计净值使用系统 那是电脑处理的术语
Weekly Estimated Net Usage System. It's a processing term.
哦 那个啊
Oh, that WENUS.
那你打算怎么办?
So, what are you gonna do?
我不知道怎么办
I don't know. That's the thing. I don't know what I want to do.
我只知道在那个公司我肯定想不出来
I just know I'm not gonna figure it out working there.
哦!我有你能做的事!
Oh! I have something you can do.
我有个新的按摩客户史蒂芬
I have this new massage client. Steve
总之 他要开一家餐厅
Anyway, urn, he's opening up a restaurant
他正在找一个主厨
and he's looking for a head chef.
嗨 我在这
Urn, hi there.
嗨
Hi.
我知道 你是厨师 我有先想到你
Oh, yeah, I know. You're a chef, I know, and I thought of you first.
但是现在需要工作的是钱德 所以
But, urn, Chandler's the one who needs a job right now, so...
我没有太多厨师的经验
Yeah, I just don't have that much cheffing experience.
除非那是一家只卖土司的餐厅
Unless it's an all toast restaurant.
他想要什么菜?
Well, what kind of food is he looking for?
他想要丰富多变的菜 他在找一个
He wants to do something eclectic, so he's looking for someone
能给他设计整份菜单的人
who can, you know, create the entire menu.
天呐      我知道 所以 你觉得呢?
Oh, my God.        Yeah I know. So, what do you think?
谢了 菲比 但我不太像个做厨师的人
Thanks. Pheebe. But I just don't really see myself in a big white hat.
好吧
Okay.
哦 摩妮卡 你猜怎么着?
Oh. Monica. Guess what?
你能透过衬衫看见我的乳头么?
Can you see my nipples through this shirt?
没有 别担心 我很确定它们还在
No, but don't worry. I'm sure they're still there.
你要去哪儿 西装先生?
Where you going, Mr. Suitey Man?
我约了罗柏特彼曼博士 求职顾问加油
Well, I have an appointment to see Dr. Robert Pilman, career counselor a go go.
加油是我自己加的      求职顾问?
I added the "a go go".        Career counselor?
你们都知道你们想要什么
Hey, you guys all know what you want to do.
我不知道
I don't.
在客厅的各位都知道自己想要什么
Hey, you guys in the living room all know what you want to do.
你们有目标 有梦想 我没有梦想!
You know, you have goals. You have dreams. I don't have a dream.
少见的"我没有梦想"演说
Ah, the lesser known "I Don't Have A Dream" speech.
我爱我的人生
Oh, I love my life. I love my life.
"布莱恩的歌"
Brian's Song.
见面怎样?      很顺利 他告诉我未来餐厅的位置
The meeting with that guy went great?        So great. He showed me where the restaurant's gonna be.
在在第十街上一个
It's this, it's this cute little place on 10th Street.
不太大也不太小 刚刚好的地方
Not too big, not too small. Just right.
前任老板是金发女人和几只熊么?
Was it formerly owned by a blond woman and some bears?
总之 我周一晚上要为他掌厨 有点像面试
So anyway, I'm cooking dinner for him Monday night. You know, kind of like an audition.
菲比 他很想让你一起 那很好
And Phoebe, he really wants you to be here, which will be great for me.
你可以发出好吃的声音
Because then you can "ohh" and "ahh" and make yummy noises.
你要做什么?      好吃的声音
What are you gonna make?        Yummy noises.
摩妮卡 那你要做什么菜?
And Monica, what are you gonna make?
我不知道 但是这太棒了
I don't know. I don't know. It's just gotta be so great.
哦 我知道你要做什么了 我知道!
Oh! I know what you could make. I know!
你一定要做那个东西 你知道的 和那个一起
Oh, you should definitely make that thing, you know, with the stuff.
你知道 那个东西 和那个东西
You know, that thing, with the stuff?
好吧 我不知道
Okay, I don't know.
有人知道 这附近有约会的好地方么?
Hey guys, does anybody know a good date place in the neighborhood?
东尼餐厅怎么样?
Uh, how about Tony's?
如果你能吃完32盎斯的牛排就免费
If you can finish a 32 ounce steak, it's free.
好吧
Okay. Ahem.
有人知道什么好地方 如果不是和美洲豹约会
Hey, does anyone know a good place if you're not dating a puma?
你要跟谁约会?      昆虫小姐吗?
Who are you going out with?        Oh, is this the bug lady?
"我爱你 罗斯"
I love you. Ross.
她叫西莉雅 她不是昆虫小姐 她是昆虫馆的馆长
Her name is Celia. She's not a bug lady. She's curator of insects at the museum.
那你们打算做什么?      我想带她去吃晚餐
So, what are you guys gonna do?        Well, I just thought we'd go to dinner
然后带她回我住的地方
and then bring her back to my place
介绍她认识我的猴子
and I'd introduce her to my monkey.
他没有用暗示
And he's not speaking metaphorically.
所以 回到你的住处 你想 或许?
So, back to your place? You thinking, maybe, hehheh?
我不知道...
Ahem, well, I don't know, hehheh.
但我希望...
But I'm hoping, hehheh.
我告诉你 那猴子魅力十足
I'm telling you, that monkey's a chick magnet.
她一见到他那毛茸茸可爱的脸 一切搞定
She's gonna take one look at his furry, cute little face and it'll seal the deal.
西莉雅 别担心 别叫 他不会伤害你!
Aah! Celia, don't worry. Don't scream! He's not gonna hurt you.
用安抚的语调
Soothing tones, Celia, soothing tones.
抱歉 对不起
Okay, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
来 马赛尔      我受不了了
Here, here. Marcel? Marcel?        I can't stand this.
他的爪子      好了 没事了
He's got his claws on my...        Yeah, all right.
试试鲑鱼慕思
Okay, try this salmon mousse.
很好      是吗?
Mm. Good.        Yeah?
比其他的鲑鱼慕思好吃吗?
Is it better than the other salmon mousse?
更滑更柔      是么?更好么?
It's creamier.        Yeah? Well, is that better?
我不知道 我们在讨论剁碎的鱼 摩妮卡
I don't know. We're talking about whipped fish, Monica.
我能不吐出来就已经很不错了
I'm just happy I'm keeping it down, you know?
天啊 你怎么了?
God, what happened to you?
8个半小时的性格测验
Eight and a half hours of aptitude tests,
智力测验 人格测验 我了解了什么
intelligence tests, personality tests, and what do I learn?
"你很适合在大型跨国公司做资料分析处理"
"You're ideally suited for a career in data processing for a large multinational corporation."
太好了!因为你已经知道怎么做了
That's so great, because you already know how to do that.
你们能相信吗?
Can you believe it?
我看起来不像那种能做很酷的工作的人么?
I mean, don't I seem like somebody who should be doing something really cool?
我总是想像自己能够做点什么
You know, I just always pictured myself doing something
什么
Something.
钱德 我知道
Oh, Chandler, I know, I know.
嘿 通过这衬衫能看见你的乳头
Oh, hey, you can see your nipples through this shirt.
或许这能让你开心点
Here you go. Maybe this will cheer you up.
5个小时前 我才吃了一颗葡萄
Ooh, you know, urn, I had a grape about five hours ago,
所以我最好和你分着吃
so I'd better split this with you.
本来就应该那么小 那是前开胃菜
It's supposed to be that small. It's a pre appetizer.
法国人叫它"阿姆兹布许"
The French call it an amuse bouche.
这太神奇了
Well, it is amusing.
嗨 温蒂 是的 8点
Hello? Oh, hi, Wendy. Yeah. 8:00.
我们不是说好了一小时10块?
What did we say? Ten dollars an hour?
太好了 到时见了 拜!
Okay, great. All right, I'll see you then. Bye.
什么一小时10块?
Ten dollars an hour for what?
我请一起工作的女服务员帮忙
I asked one of the waitresses at work if she'd help me out.
服务员?
Waitressing?
当然我考虑过你 但是
Well, of course I thought of you. But...
但是      但是什么?
But        But but?
但是 这个晚上必须完美
But, you see, it's just, this night has to go just perfect, you know?
温蒂是专业的服务员
and, well, Wendy's more of a professional waitress.
我明白了 我应该保持业余状态
I see. Yes. And I've sort of been maintaining my amateur status
好在奥运会上当服务员
so that I can waitress in the Olympics.
我不想吹牛 但我在76年的因斯布鲁克当过服务员
You know, I don't mean to brag, but I waited tables at Innsbruck in '76.
阿姆兹布许?
Amuse bouche?
跟我说话
Talk to me.
好吧 额
Okay, uh, ahem,
早上我坐火车时发生了一件诡异的事情
a weird thing happened to me on the train this morning.
不 不 说猥亵的话
No, no. Talk dirty.
在这儿?      快点
Wow. Here?        Come on.
说些火辣的
Say something...hot.
什么?      额      什么
What?        Uh...        What?
什么?
What?
什么
什么?      外阴
What?        Vulva.
"外阴"?
"Vulva"?
好啦 我害怕了 她吓我一跳
All right, I panicked, all right? She took me by surprise.
但那也不算完全失败 我们最后以爱抚收场
You know, but it wasn't a total loss. I mean, uh, we ended up cuddling.
爱抚?几次?
Whoa, you cuddled? How many times?
闭嘴 那种感觉很好 我知道
Shut up. It was nice. I just...
我不认为我是那种会说猥亵的话的人
I just don't think I'm the dirty talking kind of guy, you know?
那有什么 你就说你想对她怎样
What's the big deal? You just say what you want to do to her.
或你想她怎样对你
Or what you want her to do to you.
或其他人想怎么对彼此
Or what you think other people might be doing to each other
这样吧 在我身上试试
Look, I'll tell you what. Just try something on me.
开什么玩笑
Please be kidding.
为什么不?来吧
Why not? Come on.
只要闭上你的眼睛 告诉我你现在想怎么做
Just, just close your eyes and tell me what you'd like to be doing right now.
好吧 我
Okay, I'm, uh,
我在我的公寓
I'm in my apartment
然后呢?      就这样 我在我的公寓 你不在那儿
Yeah, what else?        That's it. I'm in my apartment. You're not there.
我们不要继续这段对话
We're not having this conversation.
好吧 我来开头好了      拜托 乔伊
All right. Look, I'll start, okay?        Joey, please.
来吧 准备好了么 听着
Come on. Come on. All right, ready? Look.
哦 罗斯
Oh Ross.
你让我欲火焚身 我要你舔我
You get me so hot, I want your lips on me now.
看吧?
See?
该你说点什么了      我真的不想
All right, now you say something.        I, uh, I really don't think so.
来吧
Come on.
你喜欢她吧 想再见到她 对吧?      当然
You like this woman, right? You wanna see her again, right?        Sure.
如果在我面前你都说不了 你要怎么对她说?
Well, if you can't talk dirty to me, how are you gonna talk dirty to her?
现在你告诉我 你想抚模我的屁股!
Now tell me you want to caress my butt.
好吧 转过去
Okay, turn around.
我只是不想我说的时候你盯着我看
I just don't want you staring at me when I'm doing this.
好吧 我不看 说吧
All right, all right. I'm around. Go ahead.
好的
Okay.
我想 额 好吧 我想
Ahem, I want, urn. Okay, I want to
用我的双唇感觉你那火热又柔软的肌肤
feel your hot, soft skin with my lips.
很好 继续 继续
There you go. Keep going, keep going.
我 额
I, uh,
我想用我的舌头
I want to take my tongue and...
还有
And...
说啊
Say it.
Say it!
舔遍你的全身直到
Run it all over your body until
你颤抖 然后
you're trembling with...with...
然后?
With?
真好笑      你绝不会相信的
Funny story.        You're not gonna believe this.
没关系 没关系
It's okay. It's okay.
我一直都赞成你们在一起
I was always rooting for you two kids to get together.
钱德 你睡觉时 你的前老板又打电话来
Hey, Chandler, while you were sleeping, that guy from your old job called again.
又来?
Oh. Again?
不停不停的打来      又来了
And again and again and again.        And again.
喂?
Hello?
又来了
Heh. And again.
嘿 卡斯力克先生 15楼还好吗?
Hey, Mr. Costilick. How's life on the 15th floor?
是啊 我也想你
Yeah, I miss you too.
偷自己家的笔就没那么好玩了
Yeah. It's a lot less satisfying to steal pens from your own home, you know?
你太慷慨了 但这并不是钱的问题
Well, that's very generous. Uh, but look, this isn't about the money.
我想要的不仅仅是一份工作
You know? I need something that's more than a job.
我需要我真正在乎的一些东西
I need something I really care about.
外加之前你提过的年终奖金?
And that's on top of the yearend bonus structure you mentioned earlier?
你的梦想!      你的梦想!
Your dream.        Your dream.
听着 艾尔 我不是故意为难你 好么?
Look, Al. Al,I'm not playing hardball here, okay?
这不是谈判 这是拒绝! 不 不 不 不
This is not a negotiation. This is a rejection. No. No, no. No, no.
不要再跟我说数字!
No, stop saying numbers!
我告诉你 你找错人了!
I'm telling you, you've got the wrong guy! You've got the wrong guy!
周一见!
I'll see you Monday!
哇 真大 比小隔间大多了
Wow. It's huge. It's so much bigger than the cubicle.
这是大大的正方体!
Oh, this is a cube.
看这个
Look at this.
还有窗户!
You have a window!
没错
Yes, indeedy.
还有漂亮的风景      看!那人在尿尿
With a beautiful view of...        Oh, look. That guy's peeing.
好了 风景看完了 来看这个
Okay. That's enough of the view. All right, check this out.
坐下      好
Ahem. Okay, sit down here. Sit down.        Okay.
这太棒了
Okay, this is great. This is great.
准备好了吗?      好了
Ahem. You ready?        Yeah.
海伦 请你进来一下好吗?
Helen, could you come in here for a moment?
谢了 海伦 就这样
Thank you, Helen. That'll be all.
最后一次了 我保证
Last time I do that. I promise.
温蒂 我们说好的
Wendy, we had a deal.
对 你答应我了
Yeah, you promised.
温蒂 温蒂 温蒂
Wendy. Wendy. Wendy!
谁?
Hmm. who was that?
温蒂不来了 我没有服务员了
Wendy bailed. I have no waitress.
那太糟糕了
That's too bad.
再见
Byebye.
一小时10块      不要
Ten dollars an hour.        Nope.
一小时12块!
Twelve dollars an hour.
我希望我可以 但我已经计划好要去走走了
Mon, I wish I could, but I've made plans to walk around.
瑞秋 你结婚落跑时 我一直在帮你
You know, Rachel, when you ran out on your wedding, I was there for you.
我让你有地方住 如果那样对你毫无意义
I put a roof over your head, and if that means nothing to you...
一小时20块
Twenty dollars an hour.
成交
Done.
你好 欢迎光临摩妮卡的家 我能帮你拿外套吗?
Well hello. Welcome to Monica's. May I take your coat?
嗨 史蒂芬      你好 摩妮卡
Hi, Steve.        Hello. Monica.
你好 招待女孩
Hello, greeter girl.
这位是瑞秋      好的
This is Rachel.        Yeah, okay.
一切闻起来都好香
Mm, everything smells so delicious.
我不记得我曾闻过这么好闻的
You know, I can't remember a time I smelt such a delicious combination of, okay,
味道
smells
这公寓很不错      谢谢 要参观一下吗?
Well, it's a lovely apartment.        Oh, thank you. Would you like a tour?
我只是客气一下 但 好吧
I was just being polite, but all right.
什么?怎么了?
What? What's up?
在出租车上 史蒂芬抽了一根大麻
In the cab, on the way over, Steve blazed up a doobie.
什么?
What?
吸烟 大麻 知道了么?      好了 好了
Smoked a joint, you know? Lit a bone. Weed, hemp, ganja.      Okay,okay.
我懂了
Okay, I'm with you, Cheech. Okay.
这里很干燥么?
Is it dry in here?
我来为你倒杯酒
Let me, let me get you some wine.
我想我们可以上第一道菜了
Yeah, I think we're ready for our first course.
好
Okay
这是芫萎 调味酱
These are rot shrimp ravioli, and celantro ponzu sauce
加上一点碎姜
with just a touch of mints
姜汁泥
and ginger
打我的屁股 叫我茱蒂!
Well, smack my ass and call me Judy.
太好吃了      天啊 真高兴你喜欢
These are fantastic.        Oh, gosh. I'm so glad you liked them.
喜欢?我可以吃下上百个
Like them? I could eat a hundred of them.
额 好吧
Oh. Well, urn.
我们只有这些
That's all there are of these.
但再过8分半钟 美味的洋葱馅饼就好了
but in about eight and a half minutes, we'll be serving some delicious onion tartlets.
馅饼? 馅饼?
Tartlets. Tartlets.
馅饼?
Tartlets.
文字已经失去意义了
The word has lost all meaning.
抱歉 有什么需要帮忙的么?
Excuse me. Can I help you with anything?
我也不知道自己要找什么
You know I don't know what I'm looking for.
太棒了!墨西哥馅饼!
Oh, cool. Taco shells.
它们有点像玉米卷
You know, these are, they are like a little corn envelope, you know?
你不该影响食欲      嘿 糖欧
You know what? You don't want to spoil your appetite.        Hey. Sugar Os.
你只要再等6分半钟
You know, if you just wait another six and a half minutes.
起司通心面!我们要做这个!
Macaroni and cheese. We gotta make this.
不 我们不做这个
No, we don't.
哦 好吧
Oh, okay.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
你为何不坐在这儿?
Yeah, why don't you just have a seat here?
好吧
Okay.
好吧 小熊软糖给我      不
Okay. Give me the Gummy Bears.        Yeah, no.
给我      好吧 我们一起分享
Give them to me.        All right, we'll share.
不 给我      那你就别想吃
No. Give me the        Well then you can't have any.
给我      那不值得!
Give them to me.        This is not worth it.
小熊落水了!他们要淹死了!
Oh, oh! Bear overboard. I think he's drowning.
抓住糖欧逃命啊
Hey, fellas. Grab on a Sugar O. Save yourself.
救命 我要淹死了 救命
Help! Help! I'm drowning. Help! Help!
够了 晚餐结束了
That's it, okay? Dinner is over.
什么?      什么?
What?        What?
为什么?
Why?
为什么? 我等了7年才等到这样的机会
Why? It's just that I've waited seven years for an opportunity like this,
而你却不能再等4分半钟的洋葱馅饼
and you can't even wait four and a half minutes for a stupid onion tartlet?
嘿
Hey
真是个疯子
What a tool.
你不会想为那种人工作的
You don't want to work for a guy like that.
我知道 只是 我不知道 我只是以为我的机会来了
I know. It's just, I don't know, I just thought this was, you know, it
别担心 你会成功的 你是很棒的厨师
Look, you'll get there. You're an amazing chef.
记得那些赞美的声音么?我不是装的
Yeah, you know all those yummy noises?  I wasn't faking.
你跟西莉雅怎样?
So, uh, how did it go with Celia?
我简直难以置信      干的好 罗斯
Oh. uh. I was unbelievable.        All right, Ross.
我是猥亵话的教主
I was the James Michener of dirty talk.
那是有史以来最具巧思的猥亵话
It was the most elaborate filth you have ever heard.
有任务 剧情 主题 还有动机
I mean, there were characters, plot lines, themes, a motif.
还有一段是村夫与村姑
At one point, there were villagers.
然后呢?
Oh, and, uh
额 等我们说完
Well, urn, you know, by the time we'd finished with all the dirty talk.
已经很晚了 而且我们都精疲力尽了 所以
it was kind of late, and we were both kind of exhausted, so
你们爱抚了      没错 那样很好
You cuddled.        Yeah, which was nice.
你们想去看晚场电影吗?
You guys want to try and catch a late movie or something?
或许吧 不等钱德吗?      他跑哪去了?
Maybe, but shouldn't we wait for Chandler?        Yeah. Where the hell is he?
是的 法兰 我知道现在几点了
Yes, Fran. I know what time it is,
但我在看WENUS 而且我很不爽!
but I'm looking at the WENUS and I'm not happy!
真的? 让我来告诉你
Oh, really, really, really? Well, let me tell you something.
你会在乎的 因为我在乎 懂了吗? 很好
You will care about it, because I care about it. You got it? Good!
哇哦
Whoa.
这样如何?
How's this?
对不起 那这里呢?
Sorry. How about over here?
那就表示有效了
See, now, that just means it's working.
会痛吗?      不
Does this hurt?        No.
那这样呢?
What about this?
很好!
There you go.
我要吐了!
Oh, I'm gonna throw up.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
海盗编号：HDT15-P1-24-15-01-1212